Oh, God!
[Indistinct chatter]
What has happened?
Oh, God! We have sinned
to suffer like this!
Isn't there anyone who can help us?
Listen.
- Get inside.
This is the last warning for you.
Badrinarayana,
our boss is planning to build,
a multinational
company on this land.
Mother and daughter!
Vacate this place with your carts.
Priest! You should leave
this place with your God.
These shops must close soon.
Otherwise, you will die!
Understand?
- Where are you going?
You will suffer if you go against
my orders. - Where are you going?
You cannot catch me!
- Where are you trying to run?
You cannot catch me.
Oh, God! I am sorry, rowdy baby.
Let us go.
How dare he ask us
to vacate our slum?
Look at his face!
How dare you laugh at me?
Who is that?
You must vacate this slum.
-How dare you laugh at me?
Look for him. Where is he?
He looks like our leader.
Brother, have you seen your face?
Of course. Who else will see it?
Look there! A painting that
depicts people thrashing you.
Hey, painter!
Will it happen just
because you have drawn it?
Who has the guts to stamp me?
Have you come?
I knew you would
come but not so soon.
Are you good?
Your time is not good. Go away.
Just wait. I will draw you properly.
Call him. I am the daring
tiger sent by Badrinarayan.
Call that guy.
I will wait here till he comes.
Call him...
Wait. He will come now.
I will not leave this place.
I will be here.
Yes, go there and pose
for my painting. - Call him...
Sit in the auto. Who is that guy?
Look under the auto.
- Under the auto?
Is he not there?
Where is he?
- Look up at the sky.
He may drop down from there.
- Where is he?
Is he not there? Oh, God!
Water tank?
He is coming from
the direction of the water tank.
He is coming from there.
I am sure.
Look there. Can't you see?
Hey, Zakir! You do not
belong here...
Yet you are trying
to dominate in our area?
Silly fellow!
You can get out of
here only when I decide.
Buddy, don't mess with us.
All of us are tigers here.
No one can enter this place...
If someone does
enter... he cannot go out.
They are leading their lives.
Why are you troubling
them off and on?
That place is their only possession.
If you grab that from them,
where will they go?
Zakir, do you need only
that land for construction?
Doctor...
- Keep your advice to yourself.
May I come in?
A doctor should only
treat his patients...
And not give unsolicited advice.
Show off to your nurse. Yes.
Let us go out.
You should always achieve your aim.
Not get beaten!
Never mind.
Boss will be here in a month.
Let us keep quiet till then.
When he comes,
we will handle the people,
in the slum and force
them to vacate it.
People come to us to collect
money to celebrate Kannada,
'Rajyotsava' or Ganesha festival...
But Ram approached me to conduct
a health check-up for everyone here.
Please come for the health check-up.
We will try our level best to serve
you and cure your health problems.
I do not deserve the applause.
Please come.
- No, sir.
Clap for our Ram.
Ram is the person
responsible for this.
I have arranged everything inside.
- Okay, sir.
Send them.
- Okay.
Come.
- Okay, sir.
Has he picked up the call?
- No, sir.
Bashir!
- Yes, boss.
I am in trouble.
Where is Ram? I am feeling tense.
You are his boss.
If you do not know,
then how will I?
- Oh, God!
He comes and goes at will.
It is the month end.
And he has not achieved his target.
My insurance company will suffer
losses if this continues.
Close it down.
Close it.
- Sir!
Buddy!
Get up.
- No, I will not.
Death.
- What?
Death!
You look smart.
You must have been
a doctor or an engineer?
I missed it and ended
up being an insurance agent.
You are right, mother.
Had I not failed,
in six subjects in grade twelve,
I would have become...
I just missed...
Just missed?
Okay, do not feel bad. Bye.
- Ready!
You are the only one who has come
to a funeral fully dressed.
Never mind. Is everything ready?
Yes, everything is ready.
I am only waiting for your performance.
Just wait and watch my performance.
What is the name of the candidate?
Ramesh Mukherji.
Rummy?
- Yes.
Right!
Rummy!
Rummy! Rummy!
Rummy...
We became friends
while playing Rummy.
Rummy, I feel sorry
about your death.
We have become 'dummy' without you.
Dummy!
Where is mother, sir?
Mother...
Do not cry. I am there for you.
He was ready to
sign the application.
The application is here...
But Rummy is not alive to sign it.
How is it?
Had he signed
today and died tomorrow,
you would have got
the insurance money.
How much, sir?
Fifty million rupees.
Father!
My, dear!
Father-in-law!
- Father!
Grandpa,
you wanted to take a policy
for fifty million rupees for us?
Mother! Mother,
we have lost fifty million rupees.
Why did you leave
us and go away so soon?
Oh, God! Why did you
take him away so soon?
Aunt, please do not cry.
Do not cry.
Sir!
- Yes.
Is he your son?
- Yes, sir.
'He is dead. Chotu is eating chips.'
My son must cry.
My son must cry after my death.
I will take an insurance
policy for a hundred million rupees.
You come tomorrow.
- Why should you wait till tomorrow?
Take the policy today
with your father's blessings.
Madam, what do you say?
- Yes, son.
Why tomorrow? He is right.
Take the policy today.
Yes brother, take it today.
Do it now.
I will buy the policy
for the sake of my child.
I will also take a policy.
Even I will buy one.
Even I will...
- I will also take...
I will also take.
- I will also take.
- Thank you.
Hail, Ramesh Mukherji!
Hail Ramesh Mukherji!
You are smart. You do the
entire month's work in a day.
I do not work during the month.
I work only for a day in a month...
Move.
Who is she, buddy?
She is the friend of
the dead man's daughter.
She is so emotional,
and is crying so much for
her friend's father.
Imagine how she will
be if her own father dies?
You...
Fool, do you know how
many months have passed,
since we started our company?
None of you have reached the target.
Targets should increase,
not your hair.
You fool! If this continues,
I will have to fake my death
and claim insurance money.
Hi, Ram. You look handsome.
Thank you. - Ram, you said
we would go on a date today?
I will come with you, baby.
Buddy!
- Yes, boss.
It is the end of the month but none
of us have achieved the target.
Still... The company is open.
Shut down shop!
Ram!
- Greetings to all of you.
Hi!
- Hi, brother!
How do I scold him
to make him feel guilty?
He will feel guilty if you die.
- What do you mean?
Sir, please take the application.
What about Ram's target?
The monthly target is Twenty.
80 more. So, the total is...
Hundred. Wow!
- Yes.
Give me the commission. I'll
not come back till the end of the month.
Bye, baby.
- Bye.
Ram, you are my beautiful heart.
The bill amount is forty
thousand rupees.
Pay and then take your wife.
She just fainted.
Why are you charging
so high for that?
What? Only fainted!
Her BP shot up, sugar level dropped
and she was in the ICU for two days.
You beg us to save
the patient during admission,
but create a
fuss during the discharge process.
I cannot pay, sir.
I only have twenty thousand rupees.
Why do you come to multi-speciality
hospitals if you have no money?
There are many government hospitals.
Go there and die.
- Shut up.
Mind your words.
Is this the way to treat
those come to our hospital?
He is saying he has
twenty thousand rupees.
Take it and discharge his wife.
Diseases do not differentiate
between rich and poor people.
Doctors treat everyone
in the same way.
Let us charge those
who can afford it.
And do our bit for the needy.
Look!
- Yes, sir.
Collect whatever money
he has and discharge the patient.
Sure, sir.
And you...
Get out of my hospital.
- Sir!
Get out.
Sir...
Ram, what is the reason for
coming here early in the morning?
Sir, please take
an insurance policy.
Are you an insurance agent
or the owner of that company?
That...
You have forced us to take two life,
health insurance
policies for me, my wife,
my children and my housekeepers.
Look, he is the
only person left out.
He joined only day before.
Yes. Let me take one
insurance policy for him also.
Give your passport size photo and
Aadhar card to him. - Alright, sir.
He will take an insurance
policy for you also.
Okay...
Sir...
- Yes.
I was referring to
the people in our area.
Poor people.
They have no money for treatment.
The old man was struggling yesterday
to pay the hospital bill.
Since it was Hariprasad's hospital,
he helped him.
How much can he also do?
It will be better if our
people here have some insurance.
Our people!
The people here revere me a lot.
Whatever I have done for them
is less compared to that.
Do not worry. We will do it.
Okay.
Sir, Gopal, sir is calling.
Greetings, sir.
Tell me, Gopal, sir.
I am coming to your
area today for an election campaign.
It will be good for me
if you join me.
Okay.
- Thank you...
I have decided to support Gopalan,
during the ensuing
corporation election.
What is your opinion?
We come to you for all our problems.
Raja, sir, we will not disobey you.
Sir, why are you begging for votes?
You are educating the
children of this area.
We are happy about it.
You have a good heart.
We will vote for
the person who you propose.
What do you say?
- Of course.
Just say one word. We will do it.
Shut up. Everything did
not happen because of me.
Now Gopalan, sir will speak.
Greetings to all of you.
I am pleased to see you all.
You believe in Raja sir.
Raja sir believes in me.
I will keep up both.
Please vote for me and
give me a chance to serve you.
I assure you that I will make
insurance policies for all of you.
Thank you, sir.
- That is good.
Okay.
- Do not feel,
that I am paying it
as bribe to buy your votes.
It is your right to cast a vote.
Serving you is my duty.
Greetings.
The persons who had fought
in our area the other day,
work for Badrinarayan constructions.
They are not ordinary people
who came here to create a stir.
Once they find an area, they
will not stop till they acquire it.
Big shots support them.
That is the reason.
That's why I will handle it.
You remain quiet.
Sir, I will fight and drive out
those who want to capture our area.
I will not give up our place.
Ram, that is why I am asking
you to cool down.
But you do not listen to me.
My dear boys and girls...
Your target should not start
at the end of the month, like Ram.
You should start at
the beginning of the month...
And take my company
to great heights.
Boys and girls...
- Yes, sir.
Very good.
- Hi, Ram!
He usually comes
at the end of the month.
How come he has come
at the beginning? Why?
Ram!
What is this?
You have reached the target fixed
for all of them single-handedly?
Useless fellows!
Do you think,
I have come at the beginning
of the month for my commission?
No. I have come for the
sake of the people in my area.
How do you feel about the
care that I take for my people?
Boss, no comments. Only likes.
Application and soon confirmation.
Cab coming to area.
- What?
Can't you understand English
despite being a Kannadiga?
Process these applications
soon and fix a health camp.
Okay, boss?
- Yes.
Bye.
Sir, excuse me.
This is my pet dog Chintu.
It is missing. Did you see it?
No. I have not seen it anywhere.
Sir, this is my dog Chintu.
Have you seen it anywhere?
Do you think I have no other work?
Get lost.
I am worried because
my dog is missing.
Do not bother me.
- Sir, have you seen this puppy?
No. Sorry.
Who is this girl roaming,
about enquiring about her puppy
early in the morning?
Buddy!
Hello, madam!
You meant 'puppy'? I thought
it was a chicken. Come here.
I love puppies.
Is it a male or female puppy?
Right?
- Yes...
How long is it since
it went missing?
It has been five minutes.
- Five minutes!
Only five minutes?
You just keep quiet.
It has been five long minutes.
It must be hungry.
It might not have taken food.
Hop on. Let us search.
- Start the bike.
You go left.
You right. You straight.
Buddy, you stay here.
Madam, may I know your name, please?
- Khushi.
Whose number is on the pamphlet?
- Mother.
Take Khushi madam's number.
Call us as soon as you
find Chintukumari. Right? - Yes.
You will be with her.
We will call you.
No. Call me as soon
as you find Chintukumari.
We will call you as
soon as we find the puppy.
Shut up.
- It is my bad time!
My phone would have stopped.
- Yes...
Who will you call then?
I understood, you naughty boy.
9742358...
Hello! What is the matter, mother?
Is it?
Alright, I will come.
Sir, Chintumari was
sleeping under the cot.
Found her. See you.
Thank you.
- Ram...
Ram, thank you so much.
Madam!
- Yes?
It has been only five minutes
since the puppy went missing.
Have you printed
the pamphlet so fast?
Why are you bothered about it?
- Bye.
Bye.
It is her wish to print
a pamphlet or erect a tent.
Why are you bothered?
I told you to take her number.
Collect details about
her and report to me.
Okay, boss. Okay.
- Okay?
Yes.
We have collected her details.
Her name is Khushi.
She wants to be always happy.
She has studied law.
She does not care for anyone.
But she will never become a lawyer.
Move. Move.
Thank God!
What happened? Have you passed?
No. Failed in two
subjects this time.
Ten subjects in total.
I will clear all backlog
in one stroke. - Oh, God!
When the cable operator
asked for money,
she threatened to
file a case against him.
If you have any doubts,
look at the flashback.
As per IPC 497/420,
the husband will be
jailed for five years
If he cheats his wife
and has illicit relationships.
Nice to hear it. Tell your husband
after marriage about this.
Now pay me my dues.
I will give. I will give.
But if I give this to your wife,
she will know that you were,
spending time in Mala aunt's
house between 9.30 and 10.30 pm,
under the pretext of
collecting the amount.
According to the law the collection
has been misused by the collector.
So, your collection is overruled.
That's all, your honour.
Bill...
- You need not pay, madam.
You will get a free
connection for the entire year.
That's good.
I was asked to pay
the price of ten cows for one cow.
I made the mistake of
supplying milk to her house.
So, I have
one cow where I had ten.
Mostly that cow is also dead.
According to the law, IPC 420 of
the food adulteration law,
you will go to jail
if I file a case against you.
It will take
five years for you to come out,
because the lawyer
who will fight the case is me.
Will I go to jail
for adding water to milk?
If I have to pardon you,
you must bring the cow here
daily and milk it before me.
Cow!
It has no standard degree.
Mostly it has less protein.
From now do not give normal
Horlicks. Give booster Horlicks.
Booster Horlicks!
Today the fat content is more.
Take her for a walk for an
hour tomorrow before coming here.
Oh, God! Walk!
We will fix her.
Let us make a plan.
We will ask Peter.
- Come on.
Peter! Peter!
- Peter!
I heard your voice. I heard it.
It smells good!
We can smell it from
a long distance. - Keep quiet.
Peter!
- Yes?
Look here.
Both the arrows are together.
Keep it there.
That is my wife's first gift to me.
Your wife has left you. What
is the use of keeping this watch?
Are you a watchman?
Keep the watch.
- Do not speak about my wife.
Peter that is not the matter.
- Okay...
I saw a girl, Peter.
She is very beautiful, Peter.
Do not fall for looks.
Only one person built
the Taj Mahal for a beauty.
All others lost.
Look!
If I have to share
my experience, love...
Peter! The matter is serious.
Serious...
- Do something.
Give me a plan to flirt with her.
- Right!
What is her name?
- Khushi.
What is she studying?
- LLB.
What does she like?
- Dogs.
Shut up!
- Dog?
Yes.
- Oh, God!
Give me that tomato.
- Tomato!
Give me the onion.
- Onion!
It increases the strength.
Now all of you come.
Come on...
It is smoking.
Do you like this.
Wow!
- Thank God!
So, nice! Beautiful!
Thank God!
Dear, my love, how are you?
Ram!
How do you know my name?
Ram, I called you.
Khushi! What a pleasant surprise!
This is my house.
How come you are here?
- I was passing by...
Saw him.
I thought of my pet dog Kariya.
So, I spoke to him.
Kariya?
I have many things to say about him.
One day Kariya left me.
I looked everywhere
and enquired with everyone.
I look in different areas every day,
in the hope that
I will find him.
Today I was in
your area and I met you.
What happened to Kariya after that?
I could not find Kariya anywhere.
But I did not stop
searching for him.
Whenever I looked
in different areas,
I found orphaned dogs like Kariya.
Then I decided,
to be a father to them
and started the 'Bhow' 'Bhow' ashram.
I am there as their father.
But there is no one
to take the mother's place.
Oh, God! Why is this happening?
Ram!
I am there, Ram.
I will take the mother's place.
Is it?
Oh, God! Now I believe
that you are there.
She has fallen into my trap so easily!
Nothing, Khushi.
As long as there
is a mother like you,
no dog will be an orphan.
No dog will be an orphan.
Kariya, come here.
- Ram!
It is my neighbour's dog.
It has parents.
Yes.
- So, lucky!
So, lucky!
Tomorrow I will come
to your 'Bhow' ashram.
I will bring Chintu along with me.
To my 'Bhow' ashram?
- Yes.
BOW BOW ASHRAM
ALWAYS AT YOUR SERVICE
DOG SHELTER HOUSE
I have never seen such
a beautiful ashram anywhere.
What is there to see?
Nothing.
Come. I will show you the ashram.
Move aside.
Business is my profession
but service is my passion.
By the way,
this is our service vehicle.
'Bhow Bhow' ambulance.
Whenever any dog barks, we bring it,
to this vehicle out
of love and treat it here.
Actually, the doctor slept here
because he treated till late night.
Isn't it?
- Yes.
Okay...
- It is morning time.
Yes. Yes.
- I never realized.
Sir, Ramesh got pig fever.
So, I cut the pig and joined it.
If anyone gets a chicken fever, I will
skin it out and treat it like this.
Who is he? - He is Manja,
works at the mutton shop.
Ramesh...
- Ramesh is our dog's name.
We give our human names to the dogs,
and vice versa for therapy.
That is what he is saying.
- Okay.
Isn't it?
- Yes.
Yes.
- Okay...
But he spoke about
'pig' 'chicken' etc.. - That...
He is saying,
he cured Ramesh of pig fever.
If he gets a chicken fever
he will cure him in the same way.
That... Actually, meet Doctor Jimmy.
Hi! I am Jimmy.
- Go away.
Look there.
Germans gave this award
when we rescued a German shepherd.
Award!
- Yes, an international award.
'Trees are needed for our life.'
'Dogs need flesh.'
Wow!
A small poem to inspire the dogs.
- Basha!
Basha!
Basha! Wait.
I want to speak to Basha.
Sir, Sunday special.
I have prepared chicken, mutton etc..
Pivot Krishna did not eat
for three days. I fed him mutton.
Sir, give me my payment.
- Ram! Ram, he is drunk.
Great.
Sir, you are great. Great.
Actually,
Krishna is the name of our dog.
I got it while rescuing Bharat.
So, we have given it a pet name.
Pivot Krishna.
It cannot eat without liquor smell.
He is dedicated to them.
So, he drinks in the
morning and feeds them.
Meet our cook, Cocko.
Hi!
- Khushi...
Pay him more and send him away.
Come on, take him away...
- Sir...
Shall we see the ashram?
- Yes.
Please come.
I have seen humans meditating.
I am seeing dog meditation
for the first time.
I am doing this for my Kariya.
Idiot! He is using
us for flirting with her.
Hey, we can do
anything for her sake.
Where is she?
- No. Look down.
You are right.
She is beautiful.
- Look at her lips!
She is fabulous.
She is looking so beautiful!
She is looking very beautiful.
She is mine.
No. She is mine.
Can I allow Chintu to mix with them?
She is going to come near us.
Allow. They are very friendly.
- Okay.
Please don't keep me down.
- Chintu...
Run...
- Come on, she is going. Follow her.
Ram! My Chintu!
Oh, baby!
What happened, baby?
Shameless dogs! Keep quiet.
What is this, sir?
I set up an ashram of
dogs for the sake of your love...
But the dogs have
shown their true nature.
Ram, is this a set up?
Set up...
- Shut up.
What happened?
- Rape.
Damn it!
I will find each and
every person who raped you.
I will shoot each one
of them on their back.
Sir, not me.
Then, who?
Chintu, my dog.
How dare they...
Have they not spared even the dogs?
I will kill those persons,
whoever they may be
without bothering about court cases.
Take the gun and start the jeep.
Sir...
- Give me the gun.
Sir, dogs raped my dog.
It is natural for
two dogs to have sex.
You must have told me before.
I became emotional,
broke the glass, and I am bleeding.
Call the doctor.
- Call the nurse.
Okay, sir.
She will give good treatment.
That is why.
Sir, do not talk nonsense.
They lied about the
ashram and tied street dogs there.
Chintu became their
target and was gang-raped.
As per IPC 228/A,
you have to immediately arrest those
dogs who raped Chintu.
Otherwise, you will be...
- I understood.
You are under arrest.
Let's go.
- Why hasn't anyone called me?
Call me. Hello...
- Peter...
Let us go.
Chintu, my poor dog.
Sir!
I have not worn this
uniform for pleasure.
I have worn this
to do my duty sincerely.
I have many characters.
Each character is a chapter.
Rogues, I will thrash you
for doing this. Will punch you.
Sudip, sir!
He is Kicha Sudip. Isn't it?
He is Kicha Sudip. Right?
- Yes.
Really?
- My, God!
Do I look like Sudip, sir?
Are you not Sudip, sir?
No. I am Krantikumar.
I got confused. I thought
you were Sudip, sir. - Thank you.
Sorry, sir.
- I broke the glass out of excitement.
Okay. Sir, will you repeat it.
Especially the last punch.
They are my fans.
Look, he will do as he does.
I will punch you.
Thank God! Super, sir.
- Super, sir. Super.
Super, sir.
- Super.
Exactly like Sudip, sir.
We are your followers.
- Do not lie.
I will kick you with my boots.
- No, sir.
We are the first persons
to like your videos. - Is it?
We are members of your
fan association club.
Is it?
- Yes, sir.
Are these the four people?
You uploaded a video
like Darshan, sir.
Is it?
- What an act it was!
You are of a different level.
- Super, sir.
Please do it again. Please, sir...
- I will do. I will do that.
I will do.
- He will show us.
He will show us.
- 340...
Take out the mobiles.
- Give him.
These are the moustaches
of each character.
This is of Rajkumar,
this one is of Ambarish,
this one of Shankar...
Look at this. This is of challenging
star Darshan. - Super, sir.
Do I look like Darshan, sir?
- Exactly, sir.
Thank you.
- Okay...
Take pictures from different angles.
- Yes...
Why?
Ready, sir! Action.
Cadburys!
I am on the way. Tie it.
We protect
the lives of women.
We have not spared anyone
who tried to kill their husbands.
Do you think we will spare
them if they touch the women?
Hail!
Very good. Please wait.
- There is still some more.
I will deliver the full dialogue.
Thank, God!
Sir, please keep your
hand on the moustache.
Why are you being cheap and
getting involved in this dog case?
You are at a higher level.
You have to handle the case
of an elephant, lion or a tiger.
Even I like it that way.
This girl is a law student.
She threatened me.
What shall I do?
Sir! Sir, arrest us. Arrest us, sir.
It is our good fortune
that you will arrest us.
Arrest us, sir. Arrest us.
- Oh no.
I mustn't not arrest my fans.
Then I will not get 'likes'.
What shall I do then?
- Chintu!
Boys!
Why are you surrounding me?
- Nothing...
Your moustache...
Please sit here.
Dear, you look angry.
If your dog can show
us the dog that raped her,
we are ready to get
her married to our dog.
Ask, sir, if he is ready?
Sir, do you agree to this?
- Yes.
Madam, are you ready?
- What? No way.
One second.
How will a dog tie nuptial
thread to another dog?
You are right sir, absolutely right.
- Thank you.
I am ready to tie the nuptial
thread for the sake of my dog.
Ask her if she is ready to
marry me for the sake of her dog?
Naughty boy!
- Are you ready, madam?
Shit!
Hey, wait.
- For the sake of your dog...
Leave me.
You still have no children.
You do business for
a living.
Such a lovely wife!
You lead a good life.
Why are you obsessed with
your house and refuse to sell it?
My buildings are coming
up around your lands.
My brother wants to
build a swimming pool here.
Feel it, son. Feel it.
It will be lovely to swim
and look at the buildings.
Sign.
I will not give this land
to you even if I have to die.
We would not have
entered this house,
if we wanted to grab this
house without killing someone.
Your hands are so beautiful.
How beautiful will your body be!
Let me go.
Boss, they are very good people.
They signed without creating a fuss.
Good people like us find good persons,
like the people in the slum.
I feel that will not come
to us unless you come here.
I am coming to India
in another ten days.
Wait until then.
I understood.
We have to act silently.
Greetings, sir.
- Greetings.
This viral fever,
is due to the weather change.
- Greetings, doctor.
It is more nowadays.
- Okay.
Is your daughter fine?
- Yes, doctor.
Take the tablet twice
a day for a week.
You will be fine.
- Okay, doctor.
Give the tablets that
I have brought. - Okay.
Also, take their blood samples
and come to the hospital. - Okay.
Do not forget.
- Sure, sir.
Ram, I will go now.
Hope all are fine?
This area is not so clean.
So, it is shared.
Nothing to worry.
- Please come, doctor.
You stay here and take care.
I will go.
Where is Peter?
Has he gone to Bharti Bhavan
early in the morning?
We could have checked
him also if he was here.
May be, he was not well.
Janaki!
Look, I would not have left
you if we were to be together.
Do not come and trouble me.
Trouble? Please do not say that.
We united on this day and
we got separated on the same day.
This is the only special
day for me in a year.
I know your heart will
not melt despite my efforts.
But I will not stop my efforts.
I am living only in the hope
that I will see my daughter once.
Janaki, please let me
see my daughter, just once.
It is impossible.
I will not pardon you for
your mistakes and your words to me.
Do not come to see us ever.
I have brought
our daughter up in a way,
that she does not need a father.
Please go away from here.
Janaki, please...
It is my mother.
Hello!
- What are you doing, Khushi?
Studying for the exams.
Stop your tantrums.
Study well and try to pass the exam.
Do not worry.
I will definitely pass
this time and become a lawyer.
Okay?
Alright.
- Bye.
Peter...
You will pay for the drinks
this time and I will pay for food.
Peter likes pickles. Give him.
- Yes...
Give me pickles.
Is everything ready? Start.
Peter!
Leave it.
- Peter!
Leave.
I will not give drinks to you today.
I have been trying to tell
you my story since you were a child.
But you drank cool
drinks and ran away.
Now you are grown up
and are drinking liquor.
You will drink this and leave me.
To whom shall I tell my story?
Peter! Please do not joke, Peter.
We never refused to hear your story.
- Yes.
Once you open the bottle,
we can concentrate well.
Then see our emotion.
We will hear your story.
- No...
What did you do last time?
You drank and then slept.
I was telling my story
to every nut and bolt here.
Don't you ever feel
like listening to my story?
Today I will not give you drinks.
You have to listen to my story.
Be silent.
Is it a joke for you?
- Give some.
Is it a joke?
Please. Little...
- No!
I will hold it carefully.
- No need.
He is drinking without giving to us.
Ram!
- Yes?
Who am I?
Peter.
- No.
Who am I?
An artist.
Yes. An artist has a heart. Right?
the heart has feelings.
And feelings have love.
The name of that love is Janaki.
As soon as I uttered
Janaki's name...
Can you hear it?
My heart beat increased.
'One day I was collecting money by
painting to help school children.'
'Janaki also contributed
to help the children.'
'I drew her picture.
She drew my picture in her heart.'
'Our friendship began,'
'with a cup of coffee
and turned into love,'
'before we finished it.'
'Janaki weds Peter.'
'Sounds great. Right?'
'But what to do?'
'Janaki's family and our
society did not accept it.'
'Janaki's brother brought goons and
attacked me on the marriage day.'
'I wanted to be with Janaki.
So, I hit her brother.'
'I should not have done it.'
'After that Janaki became pregnant.'
'Everything was going on well.'
'But it was my bad luck.'
'I could not earn during
the Dasara exhibition.'
'I took a lot of loans
and was struggling.'
'Janaki could not bear to see it.
She sought her brother's help.'
'She said that we had to do
it for the sake of our child.'
'She told me to
work for her brother.'
'We started fighting.'
'Our temper rose, and I screamed, 'do
we need this wretched child now?'
'Janaki left me before dawn
for having spoken like that.'
'I searched the entire
Mysore for her.'
'I could not find her.'
'After four years,
I came to know that she was,'
'working as a school
teacher in Bangalore.'
'I went and met her there.'
'Janaki rejected me outright.'
'I requested her to show
me the child at least once.'
'She pointed to a group of children
and told me to find my child.'
'I did not know whether
it was a male or female child.'
'I searched for my child
among all the children.'
'Then she said that
it is a female child.'
'But it is her child.'
'She said that she would
die if I try to see the child.'
'She is a self-respecting lady.'
'She will do as she says.'
Yes. Out of fear,
I did not try to see my daughter.
Every year,
on our wedding anniversary,
I go and meet her, wherever I am.
But she is hard hearted.
I have not seen my daughter.
She still has the same mentality.
I am happy today because of you.
I am fortunate to have got you.
Take. Start.
Start.
Peter!
We will bring
your daughter to you one day.
Distinguishing the features,
of which jurisdiction of
Supreme court and high court and...
Okay. Okay. Next question.
What are the types of bailments?
One. For the benefit
of the bailor and bailee.
Two. For the sole benefit of...
For the sole benefit of...
Who is that?
Is the camera on?
- Yes, boss.
Zoom in.
- Zoom in, boss.
Yes. Give me the microphone.
Final year law students,
taking exams with
the help of blue tooth.
Let us talk about this
exclusive program. Welcome.
Tell us, madam.
You are helping your
friend to pass the exam.
Our channel appreciates
your bravery. Now you talk.
Here.
- Hello, you are talking nonsense.
We are doing group study.
Isn't it?
- Yes.
They are lying though we have proof.
Hello, what proof do you have?
Hello sting reporter, Mr Satish.
Sir, take.
'You read the questions
from here one by one.' - Oh, no.
'If a question is there,
I will cough once.'
'Otherwise, I will cough twice.'
Is this proof enough
or do you want more?
Only one more question is left.
Please help us, sir.
She is my lover.
I will surely help her.
Thank you, sir.
- Thank you, sir.
Now give me the phone.
- Sir, phone...
Dear!
You?
Dear, even I want
an answer to a question.
You also want an
answer to a question.
Answer my question first.
Then we will answer your question.
My question is...
Dear, I love you.
If you agree, cough once.
Otherwise, cough twice.
If you cough twice,
I will come there
and trap you with proof.
Now say.
Is it a yes or a no?
Calm down.
We will get it. You will be fine.
Did you get the blood?
- Yes, got it. I am on my way.
Okay. Okay.
Boss, the tire is punctured.
Brother! Ten fighters are waiting
in the nearby garage. Come soon.
Hit him.
I made a mistake. Please take.
It is my boss.
Is the work over?
Badri, not only your boys,
even you cannot snatch
my area from me.
I will come. I will come,
and show you the effect
of my presence there.
Come...
But bring a good batch
of goons with you this time.
Ram, I said I would donate my blood.
But they wanted A- blood.
You appeared like God and
saved my daughter and the child.
Please do not be emotional.
Brother, enough of your acting.
Is it enough?
- Yes.
We will be happy if you
give tea without asking for money.
Okay?
Look at the child and be happy.
Wow!
- Very beautiful. Isn't it?
Thank you.
Uncle!
You have painted very well.
Thank you.
- I am Khushi.
Peter.
I felt the emotion which
I lost in my life in your painting.
So, I felt sad.
I am sorry.
It is okay.
I felt very happy,
on seeing you helping the poor
kids with your art.
Yes, dear. There are
studious children in our area.
I help them by giving
books and bags.
I will also contribute
to your cause.
Will make my painting?
Thank you. Please come...
- Thank you.
Come.
- Hold this.
Sit there. Come on.
- Yes.
Wow!
It is beautiful, uncle.
Do you paint here every day?
Today I am here.
Tomorrow, I'll be somewhere else.
Uncle, I feel like
seeing all your paintings.
You are free to come to my house.
If you have no other work,
come tomorrow.
This looks like some painting.
Isn't it?
Please come. Yes.
Where will you sit?
Wow!
Uncle, is this a
house or an exhibition?
It is so beautiful.
What inspires you to paint so well?
I feel happy and
sad when I see these paintings.
Because I cannot become
young to play like children.
And I definitely do not have
a child's heart now. - So true.
Excuse me...
It is okay.
Okay...
Is it neat and clean now?
It is an artist's place.
You should not look at the floor.
Look at the walls.
What will you have? Coffee or tea?
Uncle, is aunt not there?
Aunt...
She is in Dubai.
She comes once a year.
Only once?
- Yes.
That is why I could paint so much.
Forget about her.
Do you want coffee or tea?
You say. Is coffee okay?
How can I say in my house...
Uncle, you sit.
- It is dirty here.
I will prepare coffee.
Khushi filter coffee.
You must drink it.
Uncle!
- Yes?
Where is the milk?
- It is in a steel vessel.
Coffee?
- Brown box.
Sugar?
- Red box.
Even my wife used
to ask such questions,
when we were newly married.
Take this. It is hot.
Hello!
- Where are you, Khushi?
College over. I am on the way home.
Okay. Go home carefully.
Okay. Bye.
The coffee is very nice.
- Thank you.
Our area is very interesting.
Come. I will introduce
you to all of them.
Okay.
- Come.
Pramod, collect the
blood test reports fast.
We can give them insurance
cards if we get it soon.
Ram, do not worry.
I will collect all
their blood reports,
and issue them cards in three days.
It is my responsibility.
Okay? Over?
Abdullah. He presses clothes.
He is coughing Venkateswarlu.
Called as 'corona' Venkateshwar.
Ram!
Everything is okay.
My friend, Khushi.
Is it he?
Peter, don't you know
our level and area range?
Why? What happened?
Why have you brought
useless people here?
Hello, mind your tongue.
She is speaking in English!
Talk to the cable operator
or milkman like this. Not to me.
What are you doing?
- Give way. Why are you fighting?
Do you know her?
Yes. Hey, you say.
Listen, she is the girl he
was referring to in his love story.
I see.
- Super!
He made a mess of
the whole thing. Right? - Yes.
I knew this would not work out.
- Baby...
You were asking for a housemaid.
Is this modern girl right for you?
I like this modern girl.
Okay, right?
- Please come.
I am sorry.
- Peter, I am going home. Bye.
Come early in the
morning to wash vessels.
Such a beautiful
girl to wash vessels!
Hail our leader Gopalan!
Congratulations, Gopalan, sir.
Hello! Sir...
Bless you.
I won because of the
people's love for you.
I consider this as an
opportunity to serve the people,
and not as my power.
I wanted a good service
oriented person like you,
to become a good leader.
This is the victory of democracy.
Thank you. Thank you, Raja, sir.
Thank you.
Hail our leader Gopalan!
Venkatesa!
Why didn't you consult the
doctor when he came here yesterday?
You are coughing so much
that I fear you are spreading,
TB instead of tea.
Tie a curtain here.
Look at him. He is too much.
It is not TB.
My heart is paining due to cough.
You started again... Why?
Hello, Bapanna died.
- Who?
Is Bapanna dead?
- Yes, buddy.
I will come with
my assistant this time.
Who is that assistant?
Your friend Khushi.
Poor girl.
Do not pity her.
- Yes.
I will send her such a message,
that she will come to me begging.
Will you see?
What is it?
Is it him?
Hello, dear.
I am in the class.
If you do not come to
the location and act your part,
I will share your video
with the entire college.
Bye, dear.
Hello! Hello!
Yellamma! Maramma! Alamelamma!
Patalamma! Your mother
is greater than all of them.
Hail Annamma!
- Hail!
What a performance?
Hey, Bapanna, why did you cheat me?
What did I tell you?
What did I say?
What did you say, and
what did he hear? Tell me.
I told you to take
an insurance policy.
I asked you how my
daughter will survive,
if you die due to heavy drinking.
There is still time.
Even I want to come
whenever you call me.
But what to do?
I have a busy schedule.
That is why I have appointed,
insurance agents in every area.
They are all my children.
Why don't you understand?
We understood.
What should we do? Say.
I will tell.
Hey, son! Come here.
Go.
- Coming...
Not you. That boy...
- You...
Boss!
People here believe that
God has possessed her.
Better go.
Otherwise, they will beat you.
Go.
- Sit.
He is my disciple.
I have sent him here to serve you.
Son, where is the paper?
What paper?
- Application...
I agree.
Listen, buddy!
- Yes, buddy.
Distribute insurance policy
applications to all of them,
and take their consent.
Do it for free for this lady.
Madam, God instructed me just now...
Goddess! Do you have any other wish?
- Take. Here you go.
Child, come and take my blessings.
- Here, take it.
You...
- Take.
Never mind. I have blessed you.
My work is over.
I am leaving now.
- Oh, Goddess Annamma!
The Goddess has left.
You can start the rituals.
Okay. Thank you.
'He looks handsome.'
'But why am I behaving like this?'
My boss could get a hundred
applications if he went alone.
But with Madam we
got two hundred applications.
The collection is good.
We will get a lot of commission.
Commission?
- Yes.
How much will you get?
- Lots of it, madam.
Boss is extremely rich.
Actually, he stays in
a slum in fear of an IT raid.
Is it?
- Yes.
Ram, I love you.
Buddy, is she still
possessed by God?
Ram, I really love you.
I hope it is not a dream!
- Not at all.
I love you too.
But on one condition.
Do not go and listen songs now.
What to do then?
Oh, God!
Beautiful frame!
My evil eye may fall on you!
She is very sweet.
Naughty boy,
somehow you succeeded in love.
Peter!
- Yes.
Many girls fall for me.
But I liked only her.
You know about me.
- Ram!
No...
Dear, you should not
fight in public. - Yes.
After reaching home,
he will punch you.
Then you punch him.
Dear, Ram is a very good boy.
If I had a daughter,
I would have got her married to him.
You mean that Khushi
is not your daughter, right?
Let us go. Do not believe him.
- Oh, no! I did not mean it.
Alright. You are also my daughter.
This is a good time
to fall at his feet.
Yes. May you get married soon,
and lead a happy life!
I bless you.
Oh, God!
No, please leave her. Oh, God!
Why are you hitting us?
Oh, God!
Nobody else has fought
against me like you.
I am going to build a huge
multinational company here.
I am telling you to work
under me there in an a/c room.
But you refuse to listen to me.
If you had taken
my warning seriously,
none of you would
have met with this fate.
Ram forced me to come to this slum.
I will not spare him.
Boss, he is Ram.
Badrinarayan!
You are selfish,
and build huge companies
at the cost of poor people.
But you do not know me.
I can quash any number
of people like you.
I will not allow you to
seize even a foot of our land.
Do not come here.
Let's go.
Leave me.
- No, brother.
Go away.
- Come on, let's go.
Go away. Do not come near.
Let me free.
- Boss, please come away.
Leave me..
- Do not come close.
Don't come close.
Ram, I will not spare you.
Do not come.
- I will not spare you.
Come on.
- Let me go.
I am saying this in public.
Let's go.
This side...
I do not care for people
like Badrinarayan. - Go that side.
Nothing will happen to us.
Forget it. Eat now.
Oh, God! Power off.
Who is that?
The transformer burst.
We are from the electricity board.
Who are you?
Oh, God!
Stop.
They are goons.
- Oh, God!
Oh, God!
- Come on...
Oh, God...
- What has happened?
Take them to the hospital.
Ram, I cannot afford to
have all these people inside.
Please take them out.
Please take them
out and console them.
God is great!
Come.
Hail, the Lord!
Ram!
The situation has
gone out of control.
Tragedy has struck.
I am really sorry.
Dear...
Ram!
Oh, God!
My son...
[Indistinct chatter
Oh, God!
Whoever has done
this horrendous thing,
I will find them, punish them and
bring justice to all these people.
I have been doing service
for so many years.
But I could not save even
one person despite my efforts.
This definitely is a mass murder.
Look! The investigation
has begun.
We cannot comment
on this matter now.
We will take legal action
against the guilty.
Such a tragedy took place
when I was not in town.
I told you before.
Big shots are behind this.
I advised you to come,
to a settlement
without antagonising them.
But none of you listened to me.
Who is responsible
for this disaster?
Sir, don't we have the
right to live in our place?
You are right.
But I warned you that
they are dreadful people.
You did not realise it.
Do you want us to
be quiet for that reason?
They attacked womenfolk
and did not care for children.
Do you want us to be quiet?
Do you want us to sit quietly?
My son died
while I looked on!
He was so cheerful.
But they killed him.
Look, corporator Gopalan,
who we voted to power is with us.
I have told him about this incident.
He will give us justice.
If we keep quiet after
this horrific incident,
this will also be covered up
like all other incidents in history.
Badrinarayana will prove,
that all the murders
were actually, suicide.
Ram, I am advising
you to control your temper.
Your anger is the
cause for this tragedy.
Sir, we will not get justice if
we remain peaceful on your advice.
If war is the remedy for this,
I am prepared even for that.
Let any number of people die.
I will kill each one of them.
Oh, Supreme mother!
Mother Earth...
Protect us.
Hail, the Lord!
No one should get out of this place.
All of you come.
[Indistinct chatter]
Smash them.
Please spare me. I beg of you.
Oh, God!
No, Ram!
I swear on my mother. Believe me.
I did not kill...
You are a wretched fellow.
I do not believe your promise.
You are acting because
your death is close.
Madam! Madam!
He will kill me, madam.
Please forbid him from killing me.
Grandma!
Grandma! Grandma, I did not kill.
Grandpa. I did not kill, grandpa.
Sir! Sir! Sir, I did not kill.
At least you believe me.
I plead with you.
Sir...
Believe me. I did not kill.
I indeed planned
to kill and seize your land.
I had planned to kill
at least two hundred people.
But someone else killed before me.
There is no connection between
me and this massacre.
Why will I stay back
in Bangalore, if I had killed them?
I would have settled down
in Dubai or some foreign country,
and arranged for police,
lawyers etc..
I promise on my mother.
I am not the cause of the murders.
Please believe me.
You are the only one
who wanted to seize our land.
Nobody, other than you,
will dare to kill us.
You are acting to escape from us.
- No!
No, Ram!
- Ram.
No!
I think he is telling the truth.
He would not have been
here if he had killed.
Somebody else
is responsible for this.
Oh, God!
Even the thought of
killing us was a mistake.
I will find
the person behind this.
Meanwhile,
this man is greedy for land...
Dig a grave for him.
What makes you think,
that Badrinarayan
did not commit these murders?
No one will lie when
they are about to die.
Then who has done it, Ram?
I do not know who has done it
or the reason for doing it.
But he is a real demon.
He may be living in a fortress
with a lot of henchmen.
I do not care.
I will kill him in
front of his men.
I will kill him brutally.
Ram, I have never loved anyone
in my life, as I love you.
After father left us,
mother was scared of this society,
and brought me up
with strict values.
I realised the meaning of
love after you came into my life.
She is a very self-respecting woman.
She will go to any level
to maintain her dignity.
Now you are the target
of her self-respect.
She has decided to get me married
to her friend's son next month.
I know you are grieving over the
death of your near and dear ones.
I am not a selfish girl,
to tell you to come
and talk for me in this situation.
Even if you come,
my mother will not agree.
I do not know how my life
will be in future, without you.
I will miss you, Ram.
Madam, my name is Ram.
That...
You have come to say that
you love my daughter Khushi...
You want to marry her?
And you will take care of her
like a queen. Am I right?
I believed in the same
words twenty-two years ago.
But today I and my
daughter lead a lonely life,
though we have everything.
Peter is responsible for this.
What?
- I will never allow,
my daughter to be
betrayed like I was.
Peter... Khushi are they...
Madam, are you Janaki?
Did he tell you about me?
What did he say?
Did he say that he loved
a girl and then deserted her?
Madam, you have misunderstood Peter.
How do you say that
I misunderstood him?
He cursed the unborn child.
Is it a misunderstanding?
I was in the final stages
of pregnancy when I left the house.
But he never bothered to
console me and bring me back.
Is it a misunderstanding?
I informed him after
the child was born.
But he did not come
home to see his daughter.
Did I misunderstand him for that?
I can understand your pain.
But you have deceived
yourself all these years,
without knowing the truth
or understanding Peter.
Madam, you think that
Peter did not look for you.
Actually, Peter came
in search of you.
He came to your house
to see you and the child.
Though you were there, your brother
gave a missing complaint about you,
held Peter responsible for that
and did not allow you both to unite.
The police tortured Peter a lot.
Peter had to undergo punishment
though he was innocent.
He searched the entire city of
Mysore to meet you and the child,
and to ask for your forgiveness.
But he could not find you.
When he came to know
that you are in Bangalore,
he shifted and started
living here for your sake.
We have never seen a day pass
without Peter thinking about you.
Had you been patient and
listened to Peter at least once,
Khushi would have
got a father's love also.
I committed a grave mistake, Ram.
It was a big mistake.
I want to see Peter and ask
him to forgive me. Will you take me?
Please take me.
I will call him just
now and ask for his location.
'The number you are calling
is switched off now.'
'Please call after some time.'
Peter's line is switched off.
I will come tomorrow
morning and take you.
Thank you, Ram.
The day Peter came to my house,
if I had not been angry
and spoken to him calmly,
we would not have been separated.
Mother...
'He is the same person!'
What are you doing?
Come on.
Hey, move.
'Who is he?'
Boss, you are naughty.
[Indistinct chatter]
It was nice...
Boss...
We wouldn't have been so tense,
if you had killed Ram
along with those twenty people.
He has pledged in public
that he will kill us.
Look, kill him before
he comes to us.
He should not know who
is behind those murders.
Boss, do not worry.
He will be confused
why our boys attacked him.
I will kill him for a silly reason.
Gopal, sir!
Oh, God! Peter has seen us.
Go and kill him.
Kill him first.
Gopalan, sir, they are the killers.
They killed our people.
Gopalan, sir!
People treated you as their God.
You are a sinner.
You will not live.
Peter!
Oh, God!
Father...
Sir, do not worry.
It is my responsibility
to clear the slums soon,
and hand over the land to you.
This is also a type
of service to the country.
Boss, do not worry. I am here.
Consider your work done.
Ram, it is not wrong
to fight against injustice.
But we should not lose
our people in that fight.
I do not mean that
your anger is a mistake.
But there is no remedy to
the disaster that happened.
If you had not acted in vengeance,
we could have saved Peter.
All these days, I thought
that Badrinarayan is our enemy,
and was fighting against him.
But Peter has been killed.
It means Peter knows
the real culprit.
Raja, sir, I feel he is
amongst us and is betraying us.
Why don't you understand?
Many children have
lost their parents...
And parents have
lost their children.
They have some security
in life because of,
the life and health insurance policy
that you made them take.
Listen!
Take responsibility,
to get the insurance money
for the aggrieved families.
Do not be furious.
Do what is required now.
Greetings to your family.
Greetings.
- Welcome to the Insurance company.
You are welcome.
What benefit will I get if I take
a policy from your company?
I mean, will you take
us to Bangkok or Pattaya?
You can flatter him later.
Now listen to the need
for taking insurance.
Boss will speak now.
Sir, what will you do
if you meet with an accident,
while you were coming to our office?
Say something.
We would have gone to the hospital.
You would have gone
and paid the bill.
But if you had taken
insurance from our company,
our boss would have paid for it.
If you had not taken
insurance policy from us,
and died while walking on the road,
what would you have done?
Boss, we pity them for not
taken an insurance policy.
Suppose both of you had died
and your daughter had survived,
what would you have done?
Boss, where will she live then?
They have not taken
insurance policy.
Suppose you and your
daughter had died...
Oh, God!
And only your wife had survived,
what would you have done?
The locals would not have
spared her. Aunt has a good figure.
Everyone will be ready to marry her.
If you had taken our
company insurance policy,
our boss would have married her.
Shut up, you rascal.
Do not blabber.
He speaks nonsense.
I mean that our company
will serve her as a husband.
I meant it would serve
her like a husband.
Listen to me.
You will be in severe problem
if anything happens to you.
If you take insurance
from our company,
suppose you lose your hand...
We will help you.
If you lose your leg?
We will help you
lead a secure life.
Suppose you die...
- Sir!
I am sorry, sir.
No one should be in trouble.
More than us, our dependents
should not have any problem.
Suppose anything happens to you...
No, I do not wish for it.
If it happens, the insurance
will help your family.
It is not in
the way he is explaining.
Sorry, sir.
- Never mind.
Sorry.
Sir, please get the
insurance claim amount,
of all the deceased
persons in our area soon.
Sure.
Bashir!
- Boss?
Bring the file.
- Okay, boss.
I will follow it up. I will
get the insurance claims settled.
Do not worry.
- Thank you, sir.
Boss!
'I said I will give my blood.'
But they wanted A -ve group.
'A -ve?'
Brother, what is aunt's
blood group?
O +ve.
'It is B +ve here.'
Suresh, what is mother
and sister's blood group?
Mother is A -ve, sister's is AB +ve.
'AB +ve?'
It is A +ve here.
Sir, the blood groups of
our people have changed.
No. It is in the same order.
No, sir.
Everybody's group has changed.
Just a minute.
Bashir!
- Yes, boss?
Bring the other file.
- Okay, boss.
Boss, take.
This file has all the details.
Hey! What is your blood group?
- B +ve.
Kumar, what is your blood group?
- O -ve.
Sir, all these are right.
It means only the blood groups
of the dead persons are different.
Khushi!
- 'Yes, Ram.'
Go to all house in your area
and collect death certificates.
'Okay.'
Sir, which lab gave
the health report?
I am sorry.
Sir, I need to take a blood test.
We are closing now.
Come in the morning.
Blood group change?
Who are you?
You changed
the blood group of twenty people?
Can't you do it for me?
Do you know who
is responsible for this?
I have come to know that.
Please leave me.
I cannot tell you his name.
If you utter his name, you and
your family will die. Right?
You are ready to die for your family
but not ready to tell the truth.
I will not tell.
- Will you not say?
No. I will not.
God!
You are unable to bear this pain.
Do you have the guts to die?
I will say.
Who is he?
Corporator Gopal, sir.
Gopal, sir!
What are you saying?
Why does he do this?
Sir, I do not know the reason.
But I was forced into it.
Do you want me to believe this?
I swear on my mother.
I am telling the truth.
Please believe me.
Leave me.
Please spare me.
How dare you come to my house,
and ask me to vacate
it before my boys?
'Sir, nothing will happen.'
'Be calm.'
'Kill him.'
'Right.'
Come on.
Sir!
- Ram, save me.
Sir! Sir!
- They will kill me.
Please, Ram. They attacked me.
Someone is chasing me.
They will kill me.
Sir, do one thing.
- Please, Ram. Save me.
Send me your live location.
- Okay, okay.
Darn!
Stop!
Ram, where are you?
- Very close.
Come soon. - Protect yourself
for a few minutes.
Then no one will be
able to save them from me.
Leave me.
Ram!
No!
Come on. Run away.
Come.
Ram, who are they?
Why are they trying to kill me?
What was my mistake?
What mistake did I make?
They are
Corporator Gopal, sir's henchmen.
Gopal, sir!
I have seen our
people suffer and die.
We should not spare that sinner.
We have to attack him.
Ram, all their blood groups
match in the death certificates.
But...
Ram!
Sir, be alert.
You are our only saviour.
No harm should befall you.
Ram!
We have to believe...
Only then betrayal is possible.
He called himself
our protector but betrayed us.
I am scared.
I feel it will not stop here.
Twenty murders. Peter was killed.
And then the Corporator.
Attack me on the same day.
I feel you are the next target.
I am damn sure.
You have to be careful.
Do not worry about me.
Let this matter remain
only between us.
I will take care of the rest.
Ram!
What happened?
Raja, sir, is the person
who kills people in our area.
Shut up.
It is true.
See this.
'Hey, brother!'
- 'Brother?'
'Call the boys who
killed twenty persons in the slum,'
'and the boys who killed Peter.'
'Do not miss even a single person.'
'Payment will be double.
Understand?'
'You go and bring Ram.'
'I will go and bring the doctor.'
'We will kill both
of them in your den.'
Ram!
Ram, they have bashed
you up so hard.
I told you to be careful.
I said they are not good people.
They have committed mass murder.
It means they have
the backing of big shots.
Did you not know that
we should be silent?
Did you not know?
It is over. They will kill us.
They will kill you and me.
Everything is over.
I did not have a single black
mark in my profession till now.
But today, my life will
become futile because of you.
Are the dead people
your brothers and sisters,
your parents or relatives?
You have fallen to this level.
Raja, sir is not
responsible for this.
I am responsible.
All the deaths in your
area happened because of me.
Hey! Do you know where this started?
'The day you took
me to do the free health check-up,'
'for the people in your area.'
'Have I built a free hospital
to give free treatment to all?'
'It was a pure health camp for you.'
'But I did pure business.'
'I selected twenty people and
injected the virus into them.'
'I used them to find out
if the new tablet invented by me,'
'for the virus actually works.'
'Gopal, sir joined me
in this medical mafia.'
'So, I made him contest for the
post of Corporator in your area.'
'I was giving free treatment
to the people in your area,'
'so that no one will doubt me.'
'When I was called
to treat those twenty people,'
'because they were not well,
I realised from the blood report,'
'that my medicine has affected them
and my experiment was a failure.'
'At that time,
I used Badrinarayan's name,'
'and killed those twenty people.'
'I thought I was safe.'
'But Peter saw Gopal, sir
and I killed him.'
It was confirmed that,
the people in your area will
die due to my experiment.
I would have given
a report of natural death,
and led a peaceful life.
'But I was tense,'
'because of the insurance policies
that you had taken for your people.'
Gopal, sir, why did you
agree to do the insurance?
Why? I did so that
they will vote for me.
Fool, damn it!
Idiot! Who will insure sick people?
Oh, God! I forgot about it.
I have injected the virus
into twenty people.
If the insurance guys
conduct blood tests and report,
I will be caught.
Exchange the blood samples
and change the reports.
'I came to know from my aide that,'
'the lab reporter
has told the truth.'
I am sorry. - 'So, your role
comes to an end today.'
You have to die.
Hello, Ram, save me.
I am very scared.
They will kill me.
Please, Ram.
Is it okay?
Ram! Hello, Ram!
Ram! Save me.
'I sent Bikli to Raja, sir
to keep an eye on him.'
He joined for work
only a day before.
But I did not know
that we will join hands.
If we had joined hands earlier,
our work would have been easier.
Never mind. Both of us
belong to the same category now.
You need people
and I need the place.
Both of us want...
- Ram.
How is it possible?
We spend millions of rupees to study
medicine and to build hospitals.
Do you want us to take
a paltry sum as fees and keep quiet?
Idiot!
If there is no disease,
what work will we have?
So, we create new viruses.
We invent anonymous diseases.
And we discover medicines for that.
We get orphans, poor people,
and slum dwellers like
you to carry out our experiments.
We make good use of them.
Despite committing
so many murders,
I did not touch your family.
You should have kept quiet.
I should not have allowed
you to reach this stage.
But I will not spare you today.
Kill him.
Darn!
Wait for two minutes.
I will come now.
Hey, Hariprasad!
I knew that you betrayed us.
What sin did our people do?
One person comes
and demands our land.
Another person turns
us into a vote bank.
And people like you come
to us to take our lives.
A doctor always
tries to save a life.
But you treated our
people as guinea pigs,
for your greed.
You have killed innocent people.
You killed our beliefs.
You killed humanity.
Hey, Hariprasad,
you carried out your plan...
But only two persons
will get out of here.
'When I went to claim
insurance money for our people,'
'I saw that their blood groups
were changed.'
'When I came to know that
Gopal, sir, was responsible for this,'
'you called me.'
'Do you know when
the scene reversed?'
Ram, all their blood groups
match in the death certificate.
But their autopsy report shows,
that they had
multi organ failure. - What?
Had they not been killed,
they would have died of
multi-organ failure in a few days.
Why did you allow
this to become severe?
If you had done a simple
blood test at the initial stage,
you would have known.
Blood test?
Take their blood samples
and come to the hospital.
Okay, sir.
- Do not forget.
- Ram, let me go now.
Doctor, are all of them fine?
This area is little dirty.
So, it is shared. Nothing to worry about.
No, sir. Our doctor examined them and
said there are no major problems.
He also gave some medicines to them.
What did you say?
Was he giving medicines?
Did he give these tablets
after conducting the blood test?
This is really shocking.
You say he is a good doctor.
But see here.
There is no tablet name here.
The company name is not there.
No batch number.
These are unapproved medicines.
These are prepared only
for experimental purpose.
It is illegal to give
them to the patients.
It is a crime as per the law.
Whenever a new medicine is invented,
we use it on animals first.
Those animals are
called guinea pigs.
After observing the success rate,
and then making sure that
it is not harmful to human beings,
we give those medicines
to the patients.
That is the procedure.
But sometimes, instead of this,
these medicines are
used directly on humans.
We call them human guinea pigs.
Human guinea pigs.
That is illegal.
It is an unpardonable
offence as per law.
Look here.
In Maharashtra,
Madhya Pradesh & Rajasthan,
humans were used as
guinea pigs and many died.
But only a few have been exposed.
Do you know who they target?
The poor people of our country.
They take advantage of
their helplessness and ignorance.
Then turn them into
their guinea pigs,
for their experiments under
the pretext of treating them.
This is a very ugly
face of the medical mafia.
Useless fellows.
Could you not kill one person?
'When I sneaked and saw
you shouting at the boys,'
'I realised that
Raja, sir is in danger.'
I think someone came.
Go and see.
- Okay, sir.
You are our only saviour.
You should not come to any harm.
Raja, sir,
all this is Hariprasad's doing.
What are you saying?
Our doctor!
We should not let him go scot free.
We will finish him off now.
- No.
Not only him.
We will trap all those,
who are involved with him.
'At that time,
Raja, sir, called you through Bitta.'
'Never mind.'
'Now both of us belong
to the same category.'
'You need people
and I want the place.'
'Both of us want...'
- 'Ram.'
'We want Ram.'
'But it is not easy to beat him.'
'Damn it.'
'Doctor!
- 'Tell me.'
'If he knows
that I am responsible for this,'
'he will be very angry.'
'We should hit him at that time.'
'Correct.'
'If you go and tell him this,'
'he will not believe it.
- What to do?'
'Take your mobile.'
'Take your mobile and record it.'
'Hey, brother!'
- Brother?'
'Call the boys who killed
twenty persons in the slum.'
'and the boys who killed Peter.'
'Do not miss even a single person.'
'I will go and bring the doctor.'
We did not imagine that a person,
who is supposed to save
lives will kill people.
You have no humane feelings.
But our people
treated you as God.
Whenever a demon like you is born,
a person like Ram,
is also born to kill you.
You will not be pardoned
even in death.
A doctor is considered
as God and revered.
But we did not know
that you are so lowly.
You died the moment
I came to know the truth.
Now I should just
make you aware of death.
Raja, sir!
Kill him.
Go.
Attack him.
Do not spare him.
Kill him.
No.
No, Ram.
'Ram!'
'The whole world must
know his real identity.'
'No, sir.'
'One bad doctor should
not be a blotch,'
'on the entire medical community
who serve us selflessly.'
'Our people thought of him as God.'
'Let him stay that way.'